16th 0 2000 2 years
Unsan Police Interrogation Station
we first met in the community center
health care isn't it
I came to check on Song Byung Chul's body
all eyewitnesses are present
were with frightened faces
however
there was 1 young woman with a sparkle in her eyes
when she was watching the crime scene
in front of the bathhouse and in front of the Satek apartments
you had the same look
every time I saw you
I started to think
why are you like this
so this is just a guess
so I started just following you
true
hairpin similar to that one
what did you always wear
was found at the crime scene
I don’t see yours on you now
you lost her
when you walk down the street
you see a man dragging his wife in front of their house to beat her
this is a common occurrence here
you stop the man
and help a frightened woman
even after that
you continue to circle around the area without leaving
you were like this every time
when I saw you
there's nothing more to do
Apparently I was just killing time
for what reason
I became interested
what kind of person are you
I was just watching you from afar
1 condition concerning my son is the most important
please change his name
including last name
this is unreasonable and exceeds my authority
then tell him
who has such powers
I lost her on the beach
by the way, yes they are
what are these hairpins?
freely sold in the Mimi store near the market
exactly the same
large ones cost 2,000 won
small 1000 won
and one more thing
I need you to look after Jung Ho my son
until he becomes an adult
what
natural kindness of the human heart
people can empathize even with strangers
driven by feelings of pity
that's what they say
I want you to instill such a feeling in Chong Hu
help me
make this child
looked like you
I
I'm sorry
I thought his mother died
you didn't screw up
I'm dead to him
6 hours have already passed
she was chasing suguwan
How did Cheny Shin find out about this hospital?
she's been there before and knows me well
she probably thought
that I'll try to hide it
suguwan
how could I be so stupid
I didn't think that Jeong and Shin could drive a car
damn
how could I know so little about her
if she killed
this means
she fled the crime scene and hid somewhere
where could she go
the car was abandoned approximately 1km from the accident site
The memory card from the DVR is nowhere to be found
the car was reported stolen near Gwanhyun Ji Hospital
around 2200 last night
and you're not hungry
I can make toast
that he's not the one oh soool go away
are you kidding me
forgotten serial killer
whom everyone thought was dead
alive and running somewhere
and what if this leads to a new victim
to a new incident
go catch her now
what are you doing
what are you doing here
s yul don't talk like that
she told me everything
she knows that I left you
when your father died
and that I was living in hiding
taking advantage of that bus accident and the fake grave
to fake your death
yes
I told her everything
why did you come
she doesn't mean anything
I wanted to meet that one
who was next to you
I'm glad we met
Mother Sooyool sit down
can we talk while sitting no
she's leaving now
you're leaving
let's go
no need
she needs to leave
chunyang
yes it is necessary
I have to go
wait a minute mother
나가요
sir what happened
you look bad
get yourself together
느려요
I've been wanting to for a long time
apologize to you
Jung Wooshin detained
I will deliver to the place of detention
in 1 moment from the gloomy hatchling
you invested bitcoin shares
if I had invested
he would definitely become gloomy
what did you say
that you want to apologize for something
just
I know that the department has been promoting the detective for a long time
akim for the position of group chief
I thought too
that it will be better for the team
and was going to promote her
but it didn't work out
I don't think I've ever formally apologized for this.
After this case is closed I will return to the question
although now you are disappointed
I hope you will support captain cha
at this time
everything
mina pause
right
oh my god
wait
thank you and sorry
are you worried about chunyun
you dared to come to my house after killing seoguwan
soguwan
dead
pretending to be a fool
you ran away, stole a car from the hospital and drove to me
time and route match perfectly
I heard you don't want a child
why
you're afraid he'll be like me
first tell me how you killed suguwan
like why did you kill him
you just decided to knock him down
he threatened you
this is already a reason to die
like your father
you
you want mine too
death yes
you
just like your mother
you killed suguwan
tell me first how it feels
you're sad that he died
I feel sorry for him or maybe you
at least it became a little easier
now
safe damn
what did she say
refuses to confess
no one saw the driver in the car
she knows there is no evidence
but we still caught her
you can go now
sir yes
제가예
looks like her
what
at this woman
what are you talking about
you're not like her
if we are talking about cheap tires
I wouldn't like to hear this
no it's about you
sometimes in your dreams you call your mom
did you know about this
this is a nightmare
which I often dream about
this doesn't look like a nightmare
it seemed like you missed her
easy more convenient
get some more sleep
get some rest tomorrow we need to catch more bad guys
for Mr.
it's time at the tree he's dead chief
he talks about calling the police
stop filming
maybe that
who can use this as evidence here?
I'm scared let's go
do you want to do this
while we still have his blood on our hands
what will happen if someone else dies before us and what then
hey
what this time
damn it
the method described in his webtoon
identical to the method of committing the crime
even his place was a shining mantis
and we just let him go
think about what it looks like
what kind of interrogation we didn’t even really see their faces
he and chief chue are always so friendly
do what they want
what choice do we have
he has a strong albie
you'll just let him go
what can I do
lie down in front of the car
to stop them
no I'm talking about captain cha
this bastard
I told you to watch your language
there you go
why are you suddenly so serious
are they friends
everything is fine with mom
I can't comment on this
you know my situation
but I'm really interested in something
you really don't remember
how we went to the beach with her as children
like this
for us
everything you love is here chan
chan I know
you had a lot of work, eat and gain strength
thank you for treating me to such goodies
but why are you doing this
Pak Min has already been released
you know it seems
you became lazy after your promotion to sergeant
all those released are innocent
we can now exclude him from the case
check his normal history on the Internet
social network application
which he is subscribed to
check everything
I'm sure he's hiding something
you know about my 6th sense
it tells me something
and captain cha knows about it
yes captain cha
come on dear chan
don't be like that
just help me come on
what are you doing come out
come on
you brought me
because I wanted to say something
you
still the main suspect in this case
let me know if you're moving
or leave for a long time
changing the subject again
this detective agency would fall apart
if I weren't so insightful
and what a friendly officer takes you home after interrogation
I know you did it
to warn me for my own sake
you know my father
the only memories from childhood
what do I have
it's like he beat me
but one day I woke up
and realized that now I’m beating him
time is a terrible thing
the man I used to be afraid of
has now become the one
who do I need to take care of?
mom maybe
also became that
who do you need to take care of now?
a lot of time has passed
when this woman
was there
that night
do you think she was there
to kill your father
mom
that's what she said
it wasn't like that
she killed those people
because I wanted it
she wanted to kill
but I couldn’t just go kill random people
that's why she specifically looked for villains
to kill them
and she justified it by saying
that these people deserved to die
it's all for her
not for your sake
so
just forget about this woman
I don't think so
I went to get out
come on bro please
mom definitely loved you
why do you refuse to admit it
why do you keep pretending
as if it never happened
and no matter what she does
she's still your mom
go away
you and her are the same
hey
repeat, you are also making excuses
you deliberately belittle her
to make her evil
you forgot how many people she killed
she wasn't like that with me
and with you too
listen just be honest
did you miss her
but you can't admit it why
because I miss that
who abandoned you
only brings more suffering
that's why you make her the one
who can't be missed
you're making her look like the devil
but you know what
this is the excuse
It’s not mom who makes excuses, it’s you
it's all nonsense
so what if she's my mom
this means she can commit terrible murders
and I have to worry
appreciate and miss her just because
that she is my mother
should
do you think it's human?
get yourself together
ok
stop idealizing this vile serial killer
and try to live a normal life
find my son's killer
all you do is
you're wasting your taxes
oh my god let's go faster
this is a mess
this matter can go to headquarters
Jeon and Shin
agreed to consult only with the captain
if a new team takes over
what about her after all the effort?
to bring it to you
you couldn't even get me an identikit
I need something too
to show management
if a new team takes over
more people will know
give us a little more time
no one understands a copycat killer better than her
and it’s better that next time you won’t be empty-handed
thank you sir
the criminal even knows
that Jung Yi Shin killed her husband
Even the police didn’t report this 23 years ago
maybe suguwan
he seemed to suspect something
but since he didn't keep any other records
I don't think he knew everything
if only I knew everything
he should at least put my father's photo down
who could it be
How does this man know everything about the crimes of the ranks?
it must be someone
with whom did Chung share her past?
I already checked Anwon in prison
the only one who had contact with her was
the only one she ever wrote letters to or communicated with
it's you and soguvan for
last 23 years
it means someone else knew the truth
including that incident
her 1 kill
when she killed her husband
is there anyone else
who would know about this
wait
there is a psychiatrist
who assessed her condition immediately after her arrest
last time she was on a business trip
that doctor are you hinting
what
the doctor told someone something
violating medical confidentiality
even if so medical laws
I don't know, we'll never get this order
let's just go to her and the order
hey sooyeol
ceramics studio area
ㅎㅎ 어 어 어
oh minji
hello, you must be korea
come over for tea
no it's not worth it
some strange guy at work
2 lovely girls
oh that would be wrong
come in cold
and minjae wait yeah
when Suil was little and lived with his mother
what was their relationship like
ordinary mother and son
that is, they loved each other and protected each other, yes
right
for them it was just everyday life
but from the outside they seemed happy
something like that
it's time for me to go okay
psychiatric clinic
reason and love
the point is that this could be an important clue for us
did Chong and Shen discuss the murder of her husband with you?
you know about the oath
given by doctors
yes I know but
this is very important for us
if you suddenly shared this information with someone else
patients are waiting for me
you have a warrant understand
if not then we are done
I told you it hurts, it hurts
it hurts it hurts
don't worry
sometimes it's understandable
I'm sorry
I should have guessed that I would get sick
mrs rapak
Mrs. Rapak he has a history of treatment we have Mr.
what's your name
I'm in a lot of pain
patient therapy records
why do you need my name
this is my personal information
so nurse
that won't work
call security and the police now
if necessary sir
tell us what exactly is bothering you
such a feeling
that my head is being torn off
I'm in a lot of pain
Looks like I'll have to come back with the necessary documents
oh my god
I put on a whole show
if you would have pulled just a little longer
I would have time to copy everything
security appeared out of nowhere imagine
what would I look like
if I had been caught
you're great you're great
I hope I got something useful
Looks like the young lady talked about her 1st murder
even if he does it impulsively
but the doctor will never tell
who did she share this with?
they won't give a warrant for this
you need to take this into account
that she could not have stolen the records
and someone else
let me have a good look
sir yes
do you think this is right
what are you talking about, that you and I are working together
maybe better for investigation
share
all information about Cheny Shin with the team and get their help
do you think they will help the captain
who lied to them all this time
you're just preparing the ground for your own death
you're not the only one suffering
it's hard for all of us
to all of us
we don't care
will be revealed sooner or later
and when will it happen
remember that detective kim is a real cop
she leads the team well
I'm sure she can handle it
it all ends with her story about her childhood
sir
what is this
mother and shin
that means your maternal grandmother
it says here
that she died
scientist tire in front of
Chushin Church
that night
Mom there was a fire at our house
her mom never made it out
when she heard
mother's cry for help
she tried to go there
to save her
I was scared
very scary
everything I did
it was holding that girl and not letting her jump into the fire
I held it with all my might until the end
I couldn't lose her too
it was
only thought
she
scratched and fought and screamed
and after that day
she rejected me
maybe that
what did she see
with my mother and led to all these terrible actions
it's all my fault
if I jumped into the fire and burned along with her mother
all these innocent people
pull yourself together
it means if you lose your parents
in an accident you will definitely become a serial killer
how come I didn't mean that
I remember
the day that woman was arrested
I was the only one in the station
you must be jung ho
I'm your grandfather
on my mother's side
some old man came
which I didn't know
and hugged me tightly
true
I was raised
you and boss chue
jeonghyeonnam and jwechunog
you two are my parents
I don't want
I can't do everything well
I'll be there
let's
it's not difficult captain
yes the courier just brought it for you
what is this no idea
Mr. Hour Yulyu
this popular dating app is called Amor
signed by pack with a minjet
he follows a woman named chui and she follows him
this is a real photo of her
they seem to be generated by AI
she may have a completely different face
or it could even be a man
so what about her
look at chui's subscriber list
Pak wasn't the only one
who did she follow?
in response
jung won shik 1 victim along with kangsu chul and yush hyung
and even kim hyun everyone follows cho and
it can't be
we caught this bastard
we finally found the connection what it is
well
here you brats for a second
ok it's almost done
we find the owner of the profile and arrest
Why does Captain Hey Paesongyu need this matter?
are you crazy
this is a murder case
even our unity would barely be enough
and you divide us
you said it yourself
that the captain has ulterior motives
so everyone's attention
look at this
how did it get here
sent anonymously by courier
I gave this to the captain after security check
the phone belonged to kim hyung the victim from exhaustion
crazy bastard
incoming hidden number
hello
give the phone to that woman got it
It's hard to hear, can you speak louder?
don't do anything stupid, I'll call you back
the woman he means
well
captain captain cha
can we talk
we need to discuss something
what is this anyway
you take us for idiots
you two always get alone and whisper about something
if you really consider us a team
speak here
not now, I'll explain everything later
captain chat wait
tire vats
assisted our investigation
captaincha shefche
now
we need to unite
the criminal wants to talk
directly with jeong
their conversation will give a clue
this is our chance to catch the criminal
if we work separately
let's miss this chance
that means all the information
which captain chat gave us earlier
the commissioner ordered it to be kept secret
sorry
I understand myself
that apologies are not enough
they hid all this from us
and now you’re calling us to help
incredible and you call yourself captain
Damn I knew it right away
forget it
good luck to you two
Well, you want to stay and tolerate disrespect
that's all
and scientist shin I did it
I ordered him to do this
it's me who needs to be scolded
no one needs to know
that we work together with mother praying mantis
if anything leaks to the media
we're all finished
you know it
I know you're all angry
do whatever you want with me
after we catch him
you heard me
Mr. Chas Uyol
I asked to hide
or are you something else from us
no I'm not hiding it
this is a dating app
woman named chui
all 4 victims follow her profile
detective kim quiet damn
we are hacking your account
high probability
that one of her subscribers will be the next victim
detective kim
thank you
We'll finally meet the legendary praying mantis
Camnochs
let's go
hyuk will you bring my jacket
yes sir
hey wait
아
could grab 1 more
not a single dignity
and he is confident
I'm sure he won't get caught
at the beginning he copied your handwriting
but now I started adding my own touches
for example mirrors
to cause more pain to the victims
exposing his cruelty
vanity and arrogance
do you want to deal with
routine bending
for him to be wrong
the thoughts of smart people converge
what's wrong with choi
foreign application
so it takes time
will be ready soon
Mrs. Jeong
he will call soon
this is your chance
at least partially pay for their crimes
pac man
suddenly I thought
you don't want to see me
Mr. Park Minjae
what is this jongho
we met you earlier
you use a dating app amor that's right yes
I use it
have you ever accidentally interacted with a woman named choi?
Chewie
а точно она сказала
that she's a fan of my webtoon
but we haven't met in person
if she contacts you again
please notify us immediately
especially if you have a chance not to see each other
but why
it can't be
this is probably related to this case though
wait wait
can you tell me the joke
for him to call me himself
if you need to talk in the future
good
what did he say
told you to call him yourself
next time
ringing ringing
show your face
I have to make sure
what are you really jeon and shin
nice to meet you Ms. Jeong
why are you imitating me
I just want
so that more people know about
what did you do
isn't it fun
the mirror was a good find
I always just thought about that
to torture them and kill them
but you did it like that
so that they can see it with their own eyes until the very end it seems
you have an audience
I use the converter purely
so you can't track me
and what's next, it can't be the end today
when does the final scene end
his life will end too
I'm jealous, I haven't felt this for a long time
all my inspiration for performances
the praying mantis comes from you
wait he said
final scene
does this tell you something
films performances
as views
look at the professions of whose subscribers
kim so jun kim so jun 1 of her followers
opera singer melancholy
she's at the center of isskwangju today let's go
this can't be all
it would be too easy
he has something else in stock
need to check
even if there is a shadow of doubt
and I'm sure
that he will also be careful with all these people around
he doesn't care about it
gotta think like Chewie
that's the only way you'll catch him
or
you can think like me
melancholy opera heaving box office
hyuk guard the entrance
others follow the speakers
yes sir let's go ahead
scarpia baritone kim so joon
I wonder what should I do to help Suel
ok
smell smell
hello
please read this
long time no see
Kovrodossi Fox's dressing room
sorry I'm from the police
renovation of corridors behind the stage under control
access is limited from the dressing rooms to the entrance
checking the audience
no incidents so far
è tutto pronto eccellenza
you're almost done
Kim Seojun doesn't appear in Act 3
he will soon be cut with a dagger from the table
what are you doing working on my webtoon
you have me
am I not human?
sorry
maybe
what
how can I be sure
if you're not standing in front of me
the application can also be used to increase subscribers
I think it's true
come on take the bait
what
he's going to do it in front of all these people
this is not praying mantis style
but it's about life and death
we have no choice
do you have access to the stage
hello I'm from the police
I need to check this
keep up the good work
how can I justify myself?
seriously we came to this
you said you were my fan
here's your chance to be 1
who knows how my webpoon ends
maple act
먼저 머리
머리
ensure the safety of kim seojoon
there will now be a twenty minute intermission
the performance will continue in exactly 20 minutes
please rest and return to your seats on time
오나라 공연 진행을 위해 잠시 작숙해 주시길 부탁드려요
where did mr kim seo jun go?
where is he that he left
oh yeah, what difference does it make?
where is kimso jeong
he was just here but disappeared
Kim doesn't participate in Act 3
we need to split up and find him
captain it seems
Kim left in a hurry and without even taking off his makeup
there is only a mask on the face
he's nowhere to be found
예 더 올려 더 올려
only for employees
I'll be there in an hour
I'm a genius
Park Minjae
never around
when you need it
하
external parking
Kim Seojun discovered
kimso jeong stand
Chewie is coming to my studio, catch her
hey
you caught me I give up
that I did the same thing
that the Shin scientist should treat me the same way
damn what's going on
we're taking it away
let's learn a lesson
Mr. Kim So Joon
you are arrested for drug use and possession
Chewie is coming to my studio, catch her
then
why didn't you tell me
and my husband
well
about 1 murder
you didn't ask me
except 5 that were discovered
you never asked anything else
as if it violated my privacy
I heard
did you visit pakyungbae
Father Pak Menche
to kill him then
I just don't know
what have I done so far
tell me
what else is there, how many more are there really?
I know it's late
but let me ask anyway
Chief Choe
you always trusted people too much
what then what now
that's your problem
you wanted to help me then too
I remember
were you really going to kill him?
that boy always hung around us
minjae
Park Minjae
when it seemed
that he's starving
I fed him
when his face was in cocuta
I washed him, I even played with him
but he was always desperate for something
minjae minjae
This is Detective Kim Nohee from Nambu Police
please send an ambulance to 68 hyunro minjae
minjae
minjae you need to wake up
who did this to you
who
minjae
minjae's brother
you need to wake up
minjae the ambulance will be there in 5 minutes
minjae you don't have to die wake up
you need to wake up minjae
please help me
the victim is already in danger
he will die if this goes on
bloodshed cannot be avoided
if we want to catch a criminal
we don't need a captain
who doesn't care about the lives of the victims
please go away